minify.mobi 2019-02-06

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it. This is important; we hope you will take time to read it carefully.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small piece of text sent to your browser by a website you visit. It helps the website to remember information about your visit, like your preferred language and other settings. That can make your next visit easier and the site more useful to you. Cookies play an important role. Without them, using the web would be a much more frustrating experience.

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.

**Third party cookies**

Third party vendors (such as Google through the Google AdSense and DoubleClick program) may use cookies when they advertise on our site. Learn more about [Google advertising cookies](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/). You can use [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) to manage the Google ads you see and opt out of interest-based ads.

**Measuring our visitors**

We measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. All of that information is anonymous – so we don’t know who you are; just that somebody visited our site.

The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on. Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better.

You can learn more about [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html) or [opt out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) if you wish.

**If you sign up for a service**

When you sign up for any of our services we will record specific personal information about you, such as your name and email address.

**Emails**

We may send you email notifications regarding your service which you have specifically requested (such as newsletters or notifications when a report is completed). You have the ability to opt out of any of this communication at any time.

We will never provide your personal information or email address to any third parties except where they are specifically employed to help deliver our own services, as detailed above.

**Security**

We take many precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. These precautions include:

  * Hardware stored in secured datacentres behind firewalls 
  * All access to information restricted by password and/or secure key 
  * Restrictions to what information can be accessed via any location 

Whilst we take great care to ensure any confidential information remains protected we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet.

**Updates to this policy**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time, particularly as technology changes. You can always check this page for the latest version. We may also notify you of changes to our privacy policy by email.

**Contacts**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or your personal data, please write to us by email to webmaster at minify.mobi
